All right, enough.
Something's going on here.
I felt like someone's eyes have been on
me all morning watching my every move.
Why?
Clearly I'm alone.
Nobody could have followed
me all the way out here.
I'm out in the middle of nowhere.
But I can't shake the
feeling that someone's here!
Damn my imagination.
Must be the heat playing
tricks with my mind.
Well, aren't you a sharp one?
You somehow sensed my presence?
Although I was engaging
my skills of stealth.
this entire time.
Even while bats can't do that.
Why the hell are you following me?
I've got no business with you.
Oh, I'm not following.
I'm in the business of capturing, see?
Our army would like to ask you
some questions about Strazo.
Joseph Joestar!
Straitzo, why would you
be interested in him?
And who is our army?
Thank you.
By your accent, the cut of your face,
and your smell, I'd guess you're German.
I want to know!
What business a thug like you has with
either Straight So or Speed Wagon,
but if you're not Gonna say anything,
I don't mind having to beat
some answers out of you.
You think you can take On the blade of SS
Commander Jonoban with
just your bare hands,
little boy?
I'm almost I was insulted, but since
you insist, I'm happy to oblige! Great!
But how about I give you back
your flea-ridden magic rag?
Cactus needles!
Victory!
I really thought that you were going
to give me more of a challenge there.
What happened, little boy?
Repeat after me.
I never should have challenged
your superior power, Hear Donovan.
I...
I never should have challenged
your superior power. What's that?
I can't hear you.
I underestimated your etiquette.
You really are quite the
gentleman for letting me rest
right here and giving me these
moments to recover safely.
What are you talking about?
Recover safely?
Have you lost your mind, little boy?
Wait a sec, what's this?
What's up for this cactus?
You should take a closer look.
That cactus was my goal
all along, Hear Donovan.
Cacti are made up of nearly 95 % water,
and they're known to be
fabulous conductors of Hamon.
Now then, repeat after me, Hear Donovan.
I promise to tell Joseph
Joestar everything.
Okay, then.
When Speedwagon's body disappeared,
I swore to myself that I would
never give up hope, no matter what.
Turns out he was safe all along.
Man, it's nice to hear some
good news for a change.
I can't wait to tell Granny Iran.
She'll be so happy to hear about this.
Although, there's no way of telling how the
Germans have actually been treating him.
Regardless,
I'll bring him home, and Granny Irina's
smile will shine like the midday sun.
Hey!
Don't leave him!
Look, Major von Stroheim!
The pittal shell is starting to crack!
It's currently holding the
blood of five prisoners.
We still don't know what
its full capabilities are.
Feeding it anymore could push it
beyond our established safety zone.
I'm curious how the blood was
extracted in the first place.
No, wait, I don't want to know.
I can imagine what sort of
things you came up with.
Oh, Speedwagon.
No need to look so pale.
I told you from the start
there was nothing to fear.
Stop being so arrogant!
You've no idea what he's capable of!
Relax, old man.
That test chamber is impenetrable.
It has iron walls nearly 20 inches thick.
It's equipped with flamethrowers, machine
guns, and explosives if we need them.
I shouldn't be surprised
that all of your courage
doesn't even add up to what
I have in my little finger,
you coward!
Want to know what I think, Speedwagon?
I think that thing is simply a statue of
petrified caveman bones
that's wasting my time!
Danger! He's erupting!
It's blood!
That blood it took in is
spraying out everywhere!
I can't see a thing!
Activate the sprinkler system!
His outer layer is transforming!
It looks like it's morphing into flesh!
He's trying to move!
I think he's alive!
Well, he'll need a name.
Something better than the Pillar Man.
As his new godfather, I suppose
this task falls onto me.
Let me see.
I'll name him after the Mexican winds.
He shall be known as San Viento.
Look, he's trying to stand.
Rise before us.
Rise up and show us what you are made of.
San Viento!
You see that?
San Viento might have a future
They're doing comedy in the cabaret.
The ultimate organism, and
more like the ultimate idiot.
What do you think there, Speedwagon?
He's got the brains of a feral animal.
He's trying to smell his way around.
He's really just a primitive man.
This is a farce.
Regardless, let's just move on
and assume he made the masks.
You there, start the experiment.
Somebody open the door to
the next chamber. Yes, sir.
What?
What's that supposed to be? A prisoner.
Well, a prisoner with a mask, actually.
Is that a vampire?
Only a few days ago,
that thing was a feeble,
toothless old man
knocking on death's door.
We still haven't fed him
today, so he must be thirsty.
I think he'll go straight for the attack.
Who will win?
I can hardly wait.
What? That's all?
He didn't even put up a fight.
He's an ordinary man after all.
We don't have any other subjects
for this test, Major von Stroheim.
We planted explosives in the prisoner's
head for this exact situation.
Just give us the word and we'll
activate them immediately.
Major? Fine.
Wait! Stop!
I rescind the order! His jaw! Look!
What's happening there with his jaw?
His hands!
His arms!
What's going on with his arms?
I'd given him up for dead
in the beginning, but look!
San Viento is somehow
absorbing the prisoner!
He's pulling him straight into his body.
He's devouring him!
What a marvelous creature!
The masked man was no
more than fodder for him.
San Viento feeds with his entire body.
So nothing is lost.
He can absorb every bit of his prey's
life force down to the last drop.
He ate him.
He actually ate the masked man.
How is that even possible?
Oh, now look.
He's grown something.
Get a grip.
As long as he's still in that
chamber, he can't hurt you.
He just gained a little
weight after his feeding.
That's all it is.
His intelligence.
And what about his intelligence?
What level of thought
is he capable of? Huh?
Me, Major von Star, Stroheim. What?
But how did he, he said,
how did he know my name?
He's not even supposed to be able
to hear anything from in there!
There it is.
According to my dangling
cactus pal Donoban,
the underground facility I'm looking
for is hidden down there somewhere.
If he was telling the truth,
Speedwagon should be inside.
So now, where am I
supposed to get in there?
Vegetables, canned
goods, meat, thyme, eggs.
Looks like you've got a nice
basket of food there, all right.
Now then, it's time for the frisking.
Oh, come on now, stop making that face.
You can give me a little smile.
Lift up your skirts and smile.
You're cleared to go!
NEXT!
All I've got under my skirt
is more tequila, big boy!
Is it alright to bring that through too?
Hands up in the air!
Any funny moves and we'll shoot you dead!
Mwah!
Put your guns down!
I haven't done anything!
That's a funny move there!
FIRE!
No!
Please don't shoot!
I'm not moving it, but I've
got my hands in the air!
Alright, damn it!
You Germans are so smart!
You saw through my disguise
almost immediately are you crazy?
Of course we saw through that thing.
You're disgusting Even
my big sister isn't as
ugly as you when we used
her to plant the fields.
She was an ox you should
have spent more time
in front of the mirror
this morning big sissy!
What was that?
Well, that was disappointingly easy.
If I can get this thing to fit,
this uniform should work nicely.
What?
What's going on?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Virtue watching?
Major von Stroheim, I only
looked away for a moment.
Surely you understand.
I mean, you were here as well, right?
Everybody here was watching.
It just happens that nobody saw anything.
Put that coffee down!
It was only for a moment.
I took my eyes off him
for just a few seconds.
That's all, I swear.
It makes no sense.
I mean, my vision is perfect.
We all have a clear view, but
we don't know what happened.
This is unbelievable!
The chamber is completely sealed, and
still the subject managed to escape!
None of the walls show any sign of damage.
I don't care what you saw.
I want him found keep in mind
that he may have concealed himself
somewhere inside the chamber simply
cut off the oxygen supply in there.
He'll turn up when he
finds out he can't breathe!
The recorded film is now ready for
your viewing major von Stroheim.
What are you waiting for set it up?
Yes, sir
Roll the film
See that?
He's running towards the wall.
Yeah, but why?
Was he's lost?
He's squeezing himself
into the ventilation ducts!
Those sluts are less than two inches tall!
How the hell could anyone possibly stop
an entire body to a cap that small?
Incredible!
He didn't simply dislocate his joints.
He somehow disassembled
his entire skeleton so
that he could completely
alter his shape at will!
You know what this means.
He is now wandering around freely somewhere
in your face's ventilation system.
San Viento already know your
name somehow, Major von Stroheim,
and I think I might know how.
The only way that would be possible is
if he heard your name through the vents.
The vents lead directly into this room?
You, soldier, turn around and move
away from that vent immediately.
Go, you idiot!
It's him!
It's San Viento!
What's happening to me?
Major Von Stroheim!
What's happening?
Where did everybody go?
And why is it so dark in here?
Why can't I see anything?
Somebody please help me! I can't see!
What's he doing to me?
San Viento is trying to take
control of that soldier's body!
Someone, anyone, please
don't leave me alone!
You can't abandon me!
Don't leave me here with him inside!
Well, well.
I don't fully understand
what's happening here,
but I feel like I'm practically
bursting with new life.
What a catastrophe.
If this thing escapes,
I'll be known for creating the
Fatherland's most powerful enemy.
We must destroy him!
At this point, it's either him or us!
Very well, take him out!
Open fire and shred
that monster to pieces!
Stop the Jesus!
Ah!
He's still alive!
Impossible!
The bullets!
They have no effect on him!
He's an abomination!
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Why is he pointing at us?
Nobody move.
Don't you see he's imitating
one of your machine guns?
Look, he's just copying what he's seeing.
So, when he spoke earlier,
he only said my name, but did not understand
it, which means he's not intelligent.
He just apes what he sees.
Undsat gives me a great idea.
If he's only capable of
acting like a monkey,
we should start preparations
for using him like one.
You.
Which one of you was fool
enough to disturb my slumber?
He spoke.
He's clearly capable of higher thought.
I bet he possesses a great intelligence.
He just learned our language.
Don't you understand that he
did that in almost no time?
That must have been one of our bullets.
He's shooting at us.
He's gonna kill us all!
Let's go old man.
We better get you to safety.
There's no telling how many more bullets
that monster might have inside of him.
Just leave me!
The last thing I need right now
is help from a German flunky!
What a pain.
You'll never change.
I'm glad to see that you're
still just as stubborn as ever.
Somebody do something! Open fire!
No! Stay away!
Pardon me.
I'll need a bit of your hair.
Just a small handful or two.
What do you think you're doing?
Let me go!
The more you fight, the more it'll hurt.
You're assaulting a superior officer!
Who are you?
I know that demeanor, but it couldn't be!
I call this one the old Hamon Heretic!
What that means, that means you're...
Joseph Joestar!
Barrier up!
You're going to lose your hair
if you're not careful, Mr.
German Army Man.
That felt like sandpaper.
You should consider investing
in a decent moisturizer.
But how long have you been here, Joseph?
Eh, just got here.
Hair.
Sorry I took so long.
I'd have been here sooner if I'd
known what kind of party was going on.
I'll be the roundabout The words will make
you out and out I'll
spend the day your way
Call it morning driving through
the sun I'm in and out the valley
The music dance and sing They make the
children really ring I
spend the day your way
Call that morning driving through
the sun And in and out the valley
In and around the lake
Mother's come out of the
sky And they'll stand there
When my lover will be
there And we'll see you
Ten true summers We'll
be there Laughing at you
Twenty-four before my lover
He's using his advanced
intellect to learn everything.
Work with me here.
Make some love to the camera.
It will be primitive.